cits.net 2019-06-01

# CITS - Privacy Policy

Because your privacy rights are extremely important to us, CITS has prepared this Privacy Policy regarding your personal information based on the following principles. We use the personal information to provide you with better customer support and services.  

####  What kinds of personal information will be collected­?

We collect personal information of name, passport and visa data, e-mail address, telephone, fax numbers. Personal information submitted to us is used to arrange your trip in China.

We also collect non-personally identifiable information, including your log-in name, IP address, search preferences related to specific searches, and bids through our cookies.

####  How will your personal information be protected­？

We will take appropriate measures to protect your privacy as well as your personal information. Unless obliged for legal reasons, we will not share your personal information with any third party (organizations or individuals) without your permission. However, if required for customer service or product delivery purposes, your name and address will be shared with a third party.

####  Usage of cookies

In order to serve you better, www.cits.net sometimes employs cookies to personalize your online surfing on our site. You may choose to accept or reject the cookie.

####  How can you update your personal information­？

If you need to change your address, telephone number or email, you can contact CITS by the methods listed on our website. You can also connect to www.cits.net to modify your personal information.

####  Your membership

When your membership application is accepted, a password for your account will be sent to you. You will take full responsibility for keeping your account and password information safe. Moreover, each www.cits.net member will take full responsibility for all activities occurring within his/her own account. The password and personal information can be modified at any time on the site.

For any terms that you consider are not stated, please email us to info@cits.com.cn for more information.
